[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "ORGAN: What has been the single greatest moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "What", "has", "been", "the", "single", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Doing the Piers Morgan interview.", "answer_tokens": ["Doing", "the", "Piers", "Morgan", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "You don't want to be old and 80 and facing death, do you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "be", "old", "and", "80", "and", "facing", "death", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "CD", "CC", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What's -- what -- what -- what shall transpire?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "--", "what", "--", "what", "--", "what", "shall", "transpire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", ":", "WP", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Yes, but you've done a lot, that's the point.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "you", "'ve", "done", "a", "lot", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Done what?", "question_tokens": ["Done", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Made some of the biggest TV shows --", "answer_tokens": ["Made", "some", "of", "the", "biggest", "TV", "shows", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "Dark matter?", "question_tokens": ["Dark", "matter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "That's pushing the universe, expanding the universe.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "pushing", "the", "universe", ",", "expanding", "the", "universe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Why do you need to know what dark matter is?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "need", "to", "know", "what", "dark", "matter", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Because that could be the answer to the mystery of life.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "that", "could", "be", "the", "answer", "to", "the", "mystery", "of", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "ORGAN: Do you ever want to find out the answer to the mystery of life?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "ever", "want", "to", "find", "out", "the", "answer", "to", "the", "mystery", "of", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "I am intrigued.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "intrigued", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Do you fear death?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "fear", "death", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "I'm in torment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "in", "torment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "What do you hope happens?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "hope", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "That this continues.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "this", "continues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "VBN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "RP", "IN", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Why do you still put yourself through this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "still", "put", "yourself", "through", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Piers, if you were given the opportunity to get a great interview, a great interview, but you're -- you're sick and you're tired and you're in your bed, wouldn't you get up out of bed --", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "if", "you", "were", "given", "the", "opportunity", "to", "get", "a", "great", "interview", ",", "a", "great", "interview", ",", "but", "you", "'re", "--", "you", "'re", "sick", "and", "you", "'re", "tired", "and", "you", "'re", "in", "your", "bed", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "get", "up", "out", "of", "bed", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Is that how you feel, the same way?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "feel", ",", "the", "same", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Yes, I'm going to do that record.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "do", "that", "record", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "What will happen if I don't?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "happen", "if", "I", "do", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "You might -- you might be able to relax.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "might", "--", "you", "might", "be", "able", "to", "relax", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Relax and do what?", "question_tokens": ["Relax", "and", "do", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Spend more time with your horses.", "answer_tokens": ["Spend", "more", "time", "with", "your", "horses", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "I look 60?", "question_tokens": ["I", "look", "60", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What is the one thing, if you're completely honest, that you enjoy above everything else that you've ever done?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "one", "thing", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "completely", "honest", ",", "that", "you", "enjoy", "above", "everything", "else", "that", "you", "'ve", "ever", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJS", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "I like making people laugh.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "making", "people", "laugh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Do you like stand-up comedy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "stand-up", "comedy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I -- I wish I -- well, I do a form of it with enough good material.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "wish", "I", "--", "well", ",", "I", "do", "a", "form", "of", "it", "with", "enough", "good", "material", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "``", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 159, "question": "If comedy is the thing that really gets you going, do you not fancy taking the ultimate risk, and going on a stand-up tour?", "question_tokens": ["If", "comedy", "is", "the", "thing", "that", "really", "gets", "you", "going", ",", "do", "you", "not", "fancy", "taking", "the", "ultimate", "risk", ",", "and", "going", "on", "a", "stand-up", "tour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, I -- I am, basically, in the one man show called \"How Time Flies.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "am", ",", "basically", ",", "in", "the", "one", "man", "show", "called", "``", "How", "Time", "Flies", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What did she teach you about life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "teach", "you", "about", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "My mother was an exuberant, silly lady.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "mother", "was", "an", "exuberant", ",", "silly", "lady", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Shatner joke, yes?", "question_tokens": ["Shatner", "joke", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I'm such -- I'm terrible at the jokes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "such", "--", "I", "'m", "terrible", "at", "the", "jokes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Takei"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "What was the one from your roast that you found most offensive and yet funny?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "one", "from", "your", "roast", "that", "you", "found", "most", "offensive", "and", "yet", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Oh, the roast was -- oh, well, it was actor George Takei was given the line that was the line.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "the", "roast", "was", "--", "oh", ",", "well", ",", "it", "was", "actor", "George", "Takei", "was", "given", "the", "line", "that", "was", "the", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Why didn't you go to the conventions?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "you", "go", "to", "the", "conventions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Why didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I should have done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "should", "have", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Why didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I would have done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "have", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Why didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "I just don't think they ever had one in my neck of the woods, a little sleepy village in the east -- in the south of England.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "ever", "had", "one", "in", "my", "neck", "of", "the", "woods", ",", "a", "little", "sleepy", "village", "in", "the", "east", "--", "in", "the", "south", "of", "England", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kirk"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "You know why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "And Captain Kirk was like my idol.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "Captain", "Kirk", "was", "like", "my", "idol", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "It's part of the myth.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "part", "of", "the", "myth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joseph Campbell"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "What is the myth?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "myth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Joseph Campbell.", "answer_tokens": ["Joseph", "Campbell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Are you absolutely sick of it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "absolutely", "sick", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "No, I'm not sick of it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sick", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "No, really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Is it, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "It disappears.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "disappears", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Do you not worry about your legacy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "not", "worry", "about", "your", "legacy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Southern"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", ":", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Did you realize at that moment how significant that was going to be?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "realize", "at", "that", "moment", "how", "significant", "that", "was", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Not really, although we had heard rumors that the Southern stations, some Southern stations might -- might cut it down.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "really", ",", "although", "we", "had", "heard", "rumors", "that", "the", "Southern", "stations", ",", "some", "Southern", "stations", "might", "--", "might", "cut", "it", "down", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Is that all it's about, really?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "all", "it", "'s", "about", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "I -- as far as I'm concerned.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "as", "far", "as", "I", "'m", "concerned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "But when in doubt, whack Captain Kirk?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "in", "doubt", ",", "whack", "Captain", "Kirk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "He nicked my best lines?", "question_tokens": ["He", "nicked", "my", "best", "lines", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "They didn't have great scenes.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "did", "n't", "have", "great", "scenes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Do you care?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "care", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I care that somebody in this world dislikes me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "care", "that", "somebody", "in", "this", "world", "dislikes", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "How has Leonard managed to avoid despising you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "Leonard", "managed", "to", "avoid", "despising", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "He doesn't know me very well.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "know", "me", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Are you good friends with him?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "good", "friends", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Going crazy?", "question_tokens": ["Going", "crazy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Going crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["Going", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Do you have an opening line?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "an", "opening", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "My mother ate cake.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "mother", "ate", "cake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "-- disciples what they want?", "question_tokens": ["--", "disciples", "what", "they", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "PRP", "IN", ",", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What would you like to know?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "to", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "\"Beam me up, Scotty.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Beam", "me", "up", ",", "Scotty", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I had built up -- I thought it was derision.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "built", "up", "--", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "derision", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Well, do you have an ex-wife?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "you", "have", "an", "ex-wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Have you been like that in your life, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "like", "that", "in", "your", "life", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Unashamedly so?", "question_tokens": ["Unashamedly", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Some shame.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "shame", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 417, "question": "How much?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What have you learned about women?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "learned", "about", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "They're hormonal, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "hormonal", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Have you ever said to a woman, you're being hormonal, and it's made it better?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "said", "to", "a", "woman", ",", "you", "'re", "being", "hormonal", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "made", "it", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, not at that moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "at", "that", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "But does your wife, Elizabeth, go along with this theory?", "question_tokens": ["But", "does", "your", "wife", ",", "Elizabeth", ",", "go", "along", "with", "this", "theory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Elizabeth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "She's understanding.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "understanding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "What have you learned about you through this whole process, about the type of woman you needed to be with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "learned", "about", "you", "through", "this", "whole", "process", ",", "about", "the", "type", "of", "woman", "you", "needed", "to", "be", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I don't know whether it's the type of woman I needed to be with.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "whether", "it", "'s", "the", "type", "of", "woman", "I", "needed", "to", "be", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "But there is, isn't there?", "question_tokens": ["But", "there", "is", ",", "is", "n't", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "No, there isn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "there", "is", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "You don't think so?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "HATNER: No.", "answer_tokens": ["HATNER", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "You don't have a day off sick?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "day", "off", "sick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "-- an anathema.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "an", "anathema", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "A day off sick?", "question_tokens": ["A", "day", "off", "sick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "No, I've never been sick.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "never", "been", "sick", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "Always turned up?", "question_tokens": ["Always", "turned", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I've never had an understudy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "had", "an", "understudy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "You can't even say it, can you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "even", "say", "it", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "It's Latin, right, no.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "Latin", ",", "right", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "You're a Tweeter, aren't you, William?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "a", "Tweeter", ",", "are", "n't", "you", ",", "William", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "What do you make of the social networking phenomena?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "social", "networking", "phenomena", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, I mean, it's extraordinary.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "extraordinary", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Is one of the downsides of Twitter, Facebook, and so on that famous people just give way too much of themselves, that they kind of kill the magic?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "one", "of", "the", "downsides", "of", "Twitter", ",", "Facebook", ",", "and", "so", "on", "that", "famous", "people", "just", "give", "way", "too", "much", "of", "themselves", ",", "that", "they", "kind", "of", "kill", "the", "magic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers Morgan"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What would you -- what would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "--", "what", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Doing a Piers Morgan interview.", "answer_tokens": ["Doing", "a", "Piers", "Morgan", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Can you replicate that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "replicate", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Well, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", ":", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What's been the greatest professional moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "greatest", "professional", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "There are -- Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "--", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Is that what it's all about?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "it", "'s", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "And do you live for those moments?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "live", "for", "those", "moments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "What are you going to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "I don't know what they're going to do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "But if you could, how are you seeing it all unraveling now?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "could", ",", "how", "are", "you", "seeing", "it", "all", "unraveling", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Well, it's totally -- it's fraught with terrible decisions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "totally", "--", "it", "'s", "fraught", "with", "terrible", "decisions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Do you think you're a good singer or you're an entertainer?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "a", "good", "singer", "or", "you", "'re", "an", "entertainer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "HATNER: Oh, no, no, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["HATNER", ":", "Oh", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Does it ever stray into singing, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "ever", "stray", "into", "singing", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Is it an early form of rap?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "an", "early", "form", "of", "rap", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Where do you want to boldly go to next?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "want", "to", "boldly", "go", "to", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "I'm going to go next door.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "next", "door", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "That decision, was that the greatest decision you've ever taken?", "question_tokens": ["That", "decision", ",", "was", "that", "the", "greatest", "decision", "you", "'ve", "ever", "taken", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "It could have been.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "could", "have", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "But when you watched the stock going up, what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "watched", "the", "stock", "going", "up", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I thought, I'm rich, I'm beyond -- beyond any concept of being rich.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", ",", "I", "'m", "rich", ",", "I", "'m", "beyond", "--", "beyond", "any", "concept", "of", "being", "rich", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "Was your decision to sell your stock, when it bottomed out, the worst decision of your life?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "your", "decision", "to", "sell", "your", "stock", ",", "when", "it", "bottomed", "out", ",", "the", "worst", "decision", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "It was the only intelligent decision to make.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "the", "only", "intelligent", "decision", "to", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Well, what happened -- can you think of another dot-com company that exists?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "happened", "--", "can", "you", "think", "of", "another", "dot-com", "company", "that", "exists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "A few.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "few", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["DVD"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "So, all this sort of impression that you're this billionaire, actually, you need to sell a few records, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "all", "this", "sort", "of", "impression", "that", "you", "'re", "this", "billionaire", ",", "actually", ",", "you", "need", "to", "sell", "a", "few", "records", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "You've got to buy my record, and a few books, and the DVD.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "to", "buy", "my", "record", ",", "and", "a", "few", "books", ",", "and", "the", "DVD", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Canada"]}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Anything else?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "And come in Canada when I do the one-man show.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "come", "in", "Canada", "when", "I", "do", "the", "one-man", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "Shall we just beam ourselves out of here?", "question_tokens": ["Shall", "we", "just", "beam", "ourselves", "out", "of", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "Get out of here.", "answer_tokens": ["Get", "out", "of", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]